Vanesa González

PROFILE

Studies in Graphic Design at the Kensington and Chelsea College in London.

Extensive knowledge in Art and History due to a previous education.

Currently working as a freelance tour guide in London for Spanish speakers.

Also, experience in customer service and customer support.

CONTACT DETAILS



🔀 vanesa.designer@gmail.com

MORE INFO

www.vanesadesigner.com



EDUCATION

SKILLS

BTEC Level 3 diploma in Art and Design - Graphic Design at the Kensington and Chelsea College (2015-2017)

Completed three out of five years in History of Art Degree at the Complutense University of Madrid (2000-2006, interrupted due to professional commitments)

COMPLEMENTARY STUDIES

Photography, Level I (different techniques and photographic language) (Fotoaula School, Madrid)

History of Photography (Faculty of Geography and History, U.C.M.)

Appraisal and Survey of Art Works (Faculty of Geography and History, U.C.M.)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Current Position: Freelance tour guide

Dates: 2015 to present

Providing services as a tour guide to Spanish speakers for two different companies (Sandemans New Europe Tours and Tour Londres)

Employer: Digitex S.A. Dates: 2005-2014

Position: Customer Services Assistant

Managed two important accounts for major customers and

coordinated with suppliers to fulfil tight deadlines

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Permission to work in the UK (UE citizen) Current address: Flat B 31 Park Road, N8 8TE, London Hobbies: Art, Photography, Cinema, Music, Reading